<resources>
    <string name="app_name">"30 Days of Reading"</string>

    <string name="title_1">"Amir and his Dad on Sin."</string>
    <string name="title_2">"Amir and Hassan, the sultans of Kabul."</string>
    <string name="title_3">"Amir with Hassan's Son."</string>
    <string name="title_4">"Pari, Abdullah and their father Saboor."</string>
    <string name="title_5">"Abdullah on Waiting"</string>
    <string name="title_6">"And The Mountains Echoed"</string>
    <string name="title_7">"Mariam on his mother"</string>
    <string name="title_8">"Pari on his mother"</string>
    <string name="title_9">"Tyroin Lanister"</string>
    <string name="title_10">"Ned Stark to his son's"</string>
    <string name="title_11">"Red Wedding"</string>
    <string name="title_12">"The King in the North"</string>
    <string name="title_13">"The Rogue Prince"</string>
    <string name="title_14">"The Father"</string>
    <string name="title_15">"True Heir of the Iron Throne"</string>
    <string name="title_16">"Ted and Robin in Love"</string>
    <string name="title_17">"Barney and His Daughter"</string>
    <string name="title_18">"World's Greatest Couple"</string>
    <string name="title_19">"A Man who drinks Tea"</string>
    <string name="title_20">"Eldest Shelby"</string>
    <string name="title_21">"The Song of Achilles"</string>
    <string name="title_22">"GoodBye?"</string>
    <string name="title_23">"Silence!"</string>
    <string name="title_24">"Home"</string>
    <string name="title_25">"Bankai"</string>
    <string name="title_26">"God?"</string>
    <string name="title_27">"Dance"</string>
    <string name="title_28">"Holding Someone"</string>
    <string name="title_29">"Murakami"</string>
    <string name="title_30">"Relevant Love"</string>

    <string name="quote_1">"There is only one sin and that is theft... When you kill a man, you steal a life. You steal his wife's right to a husband, rob his children of a father. When you tell a lie, you steal someone's right to the truth. When you cheat, you steal the right to fairness."</string>
    <string name="quote_2">"Hassan couldn't read a first-grade textbook but he'd read me plenty. That was a little unsettling but also sort of comfortable to have someone who always knew what you needed."</string>
    <string name="quote_3">"For you, a thousand times over. Then I turned and ran. It was only a smile, nothing more. It did not make everything alright. But I'll take it. With open arms."</string>
    <string name="quote_4">"Out beyond ideas, of wrongdoing and right doing,
there is a field. I’ll meet you there."</string>
    <string name="quote_5">"I suspect the truth is that we are waiting, all of us, against insurmountable odds, for something extraordinary to happen to us."</string>
    <string name="quote_6">"I learned that the world didn't see the inside of you, that it didn't care a whit about the hopes and dreams, and sorrows, that lay masked by skin and bone. It was as simple, as absurd, and as cruel as that."</string>
    <string name="quote_7">"One could not count the moons that shimmer on her roofs,
Or the thousand splendid suns that hide behind her walls."</string>
    <string name="quote_8">"Of all the hardships a person had to face, none was more punishing than the simple act of waiting."</string>
    <string name="quote_9">"Never Forget What You Are, The Rest Of The World Will Not. Wear It Like Armor, And It Can Never Be Used To Hurt You."</string>
    <string name="quote_10">"The man who passes the sentence should swing the sword. If you would take a man's life, you owe it to him to look into his eyes and hear his final words. And if you cannot bear to do that, then perhaps the man does not deserve to die."</string>
    <string name="quote_11">"Love is the bane of honor, the death of duty. What is honor compared to a woman's love? What is duty against the feel of a newborn son in your arms ... or the memory of a brother's smile? Wind and words. Wind and words. We are only human, and the gods have fashioned us for love. That is our great glory, and our great tragedy."</string>
    <string name="quote_12">"We know no King but the King of the North whose name is Stark. I don't care if he's a bastard. Ned Stark's blood runs through his veins. He's my king–from this day until his last day."</string>
    <string name="quote_13">"Dreams didn't make us kings.... dragons did"</string>
    <string name="quote_14">"I Will Sit The Throne Today."</string>
    <string name="quote_15">"Will you not weep?"
    “I do not have the time for tears.”</string>
    <string name="quote_16">"You will be shocked, kids when you discover how easy it is in life to part ways with people forever. That's why, when you find someone you want to keep around, you do something about it."</string>
    <string name="quote_17">"You are the love of my life. Everything I have and everything I am is yours. Forever."</string>
    <string name="quote_18">"Lily, There Are A Million Reasons Why I Love You. You Make Me Laugh, You Take Care Of Me When I'm Sick, You're Sweet, Caring, And You Even Created An Egg Dish And Named It After Me. ... But The Main Reason Is You're My Best Friend, Lily. You're The Best Friend I Ever Had."</string>
    <string name="quote_19">"My plan was that we sit here for a while, talk about old times, drink some whiskey. Then I was gonna tell you... I hadn't spent a day without thinking about you."</string>
    <string name="quote_20">"I am a good man. There is good in my heart. But my hands? These hands belong to the devil."</string>
    <string name="quote_21">"Name one hero who was happy. You can't. I can't. I know. They never let you be famous and happy. I'll tell you a secret. Tell me. I'm going to be the first. Swear it. Why me? Because you're the reason. Swear it. I swear it"</string>
    <string name="quote_22">"Goodbyes are only for those who love with their eyes. Because for those who love with heart and soul there is no such thing as separation."</string>
    <string name="quote_23">"Don't try to find a reason for somebody's love"</string>
    <string name="quote_24">"A place where someone still thinks about you is a place you can call home."</string>
    <string name="quote_25">"Where do you think you are going? Who do you think I am? Supreme Commander of Gotai 13 "Shunsui Kyoraku" The world will not protect you from me."</string>
    <string name="quote_26">"I don’t believe in the gods’ existence. Man is the master of his own fate, not the gods. The gods are man’s creation to give answers that they are too afraid to give themselves."</string>
    <string name="quote_27">"When people start dancing, they dance like they don't know they are doing it."</string>
    <string name="quote_28">"You think that holding someone hard will bring them closer. You think that you can hold them so hard that you'll still feel them, embossed on you, when you pull away."</string>
    <string name="quote_29">"Who can really distinguish between the sea and what's reflected in it? Or tell the difference between the falling rain and loneliness?"</string>
    <string name="quote_30">"you might not have been my first love but you were the love that made all the other loves irrelevant"</string>

    <string name="author_1">― Khaled Hosseini, The Kite Runner</string>
    <string name="author_2">― Khaled Hosseini, The Kite Runner</string>
    <string name="author_3">― Khaled Hosseini, The Kite Runner</string>
    <string name="author_4">― Rumi</string>
    <string name="author_5">― Khaled Hosseini, And the Mountains Echoed</string>
    <string name="author_6">― Khaled Hosseini, And the Mountains Echoed</string>
    <string name="author_7">― Khaled Hosseini, A Thousand Splendid Suns</string>
    <string name="author_8">― Khaled Hosseini, A Thousand Splendid Suns</string>
    <string name="author_9">― Tyrion Lannister, Game of Thrones</string>
    <string name="author_10">― Ned Stark, Game of Thrones</string>
    <string name="author_11">― Aemon Targaryen, Game of Thrones</string>
    <string name="author_12">― Lyanna Mormont, Game of Thrones</string>
    <string name="author_13">― Daemon Targaryen, House of the Dragon</string>
    <string name="author_14">― Viserys Targaryen, House of the Dragon</string>
    <string name="author_15">― Rhaenyra Targaryen, Fire &amp; Blood</string>
    <string name="author_16">― Ted Mosby, How I Met Your Mother</string>
    <string name="author_17">― Barny Stinson, How I Met Your Mother</string>
    <string name="author_18">― Marshal Ericson, How I Met Your Mother</string>
    <string name="author_19">― Thomas Shelby, Peaky Blinders</string>
    <string name="author_20">― Arthur Shelby, Peaky Blinders</string>
    <string name="author_21">― Madeline Miller, The Song of Achilles</string>
    <string name="author_22">― Rumi</string>
    <string name="author_23">― Sengoku, One Piece</string>
    <string name="author_24">― Jiraya, Naruto </string>
    <string name="author_25">― Shunsui Kyoraku, Bleach</string>
    <string name="author_26">― Ragnar LothBrok, Vikings</string>
    <string name="author_27">― Nushrat Fateh Ali Khan</string>
    <string name="author_28">― Rainbow Rowell, Eleanor &amp; Park</string>
    <string name="author_29">― Haruki Murakami, Sputnik Sweetheart</string>
    <string name="author_30">― Rupi Kaur</string>

</resources>